(1967年)
警察在街上找到她
Police found her in the street.
看起来 她像是被什么动物咬到
Looks like she was bitten. Some kind of an animal.
老天 羊水破了 她的子宫收缩
Jesus! Her water's broken! She's going into uterine contractions!
必须剖腹生产
We'll have to do a C-section!
《刀锋战士》
(现今)
- 小老弟 那是什么?  - 我的感热导弹
- What you got down there, little man?  - Oh, that's my heatseeker.
一定很猛
I'll bet it is.
- 我们上哪里?  - 这是个惊喜
- So, where are we going?  - It's a surprise, baby.
我最爱惊喜
Yeah, I like surprises.
我的天
Oh, my God!
跑来这儿干嘛?
What the fuck are we doing here?
你瞧瞧
Look at all that.
什么鬼玩意?
What the fuck is that?
你跟他说些什么?
What did you just say?
愉快吗? 哥们
What's up? Man!
怎么了?
What's happening?
妈的
Fuck.
我得喝杯酒
Fuck. I need a drink.
(血浴)
不 不
No! No!
怎么了 小帅哥?
What's wrong, baby?
不 不
No! No!
不
No!
是他吗?
Is that him?
老天 是他
Jesus, that's him.
刀锋 日行者
It's Blade. It's the daywalker.
来吧 日行者
Come on, daywalker!
我要扭断你脑袋
I'm gonna rip your fucking head off!
就是他 大伙上 把他干掉
That's him! Get him! Fuck him up!
我要痛宰你 让他断手断脚
We're gonna jack you up. Make him hurt bad.
昆恩
Quinn...
我已经砍你砍得手酸了
I'm getting a little tired of chopping you up.
这次我想换换口味 用火烧
Thought I might try fire for a change.
替我向弗劳斯特问好
Give my regards to Frost.
别杀我 求求你
Don't! Please don't!
快灭火
Put him out.
- 是 先生  - 医护人员  借过
- Yes, sir.  - Paramedics.
有一具焦尸 还热腾腾的
Got a charred cadaver for you. Still warm, too.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
老天 好臭
Oh, Jesus, that's rank.
他被发现时还在惨叫...
He was still screaming when they found him...
他被钉在墙上
stapled to a wall.
真是个帅哥
That's very pretty.
(血液学医师 卡伦·杰森)
替他验过血吗?
Did you check the chem count?
血糖高于正常三倍...
His blood sugar's 3 times norm...
亚磷酸和尿酸也很高
phosphorus and uric acid are offthe charts.
就是那名死者?
You took this off a DOA?
这不合常理
But this doesn't make any sense.
他有双凸红血球 不可能
The red blood cells are biconvex, which is impossible.
你看 多形核白血球
Look at the polys, they're binucleated.
别耍我 寇特斯
OK. Curtis,
- 半夜三点了  - 我没耍你
- it's 3:00 in the morning  - This is not a joke.
尸体现在就在停尸间
I've got the body in the morgue right now.
你答应过不会纠缠我
I thought you promised to give me some distance.
我只想请你来看一下
I just want you to come down and take a look.
好 给我看吧 不过别想跟我复合
OK. Show me the body. And I don't want to hear a word about us.
好啦 我们都谈过了
Done. We've had that conversation.
你还没解剖内脏?
You haven't started on the internal organs yet?
只替他验过血
Just a blood sample for the pericardium.
上颔骨有点畸形
The maxilla looks a little deformed.
犬齿有点奇怪
There's some odd muscle structure around the canines.
我要剖开检查气管黏膜
I'm going to start the "Y" and check the tracheal mucosa.
我想问你点事
Let me ask you something.
老实说...
Honestly...
有没有后悔跟我分手?
you ever have second thoughts about us?
有时候
Sometimes.
不过我马上想到你是个浑蛋
But then I remember how much of an asshole you were.
拜托你 公平点?
Want to cut me some slack here?
你要时间考虑 我答应了
You asked for some time off, I gave you some time off.
寇特斯…
Look, Curtis...
- 我会改  - 我们吹了
- I'm trying.  - It's over.
快叫保安
Call security!
- 我回来解决你  - 给我滚开 怪胎
- Came back to finish you off.  - Get out of my way, you freak!
别动
Freeze!
该死的 你们疯啦
Motherfucker, are you out of your damn mind?!
你 站住
Hey, you! Freeze!
站住
Freeze!
站那别动
Hold it right there!
我的肩膀…
My shoulder...
脱臼了
it's dislocated.
惠斯勒
Whistler.
你把流浪狗带回家?
Bringing home strays now?
她被咬过
She's been bitten.
- 你应该杀了她  - 我知道...
- Should've killed her, then.  - Yeah, I know...
不过我没有
but I didn't.
好好看着她 若她变吸血鬼 就杀了她
You watch her close. If she starts to turn, you finish her off.
否则我会下手
Or I will.
她没有救了
She's borderline.
一小时后就会变
Another hour, she'd be well into the change.
卡伦·杰森医师 听好
Dr. Karen Jenson, listen close.
我替你注射艾林萨顿…
I'm going to inject you with allium sativum...
蒜精 这会很痛
garlic. This is going to hurt... a lot.
- 是昆恩  - 弗劳斯特的跑腿小弟?
- It was Quinn.  - Frost's little errand boy?
找到他的巢穴吗?
You get a lead on him?
没有
No.
真可惜
Too bad.
按住她
Hold her.
一旦她熬过今晚 那就有五成机会
I give her fifty-fifty if she makes it through the night.
刀锋 日行者…
Blade, the daywalker...
他妄想要消灭吸血族
still pursuing his ridiculous crusade.
死了多少?
How many died?
多得数不清
We don't have an exact count.
他用很了多银钉
Apparently, he used a lot of silver.
我们有麻烦了…
We're having difficulty...
叫弗劳斯特进来
Send in Frost.
狄肯·弗劳斯特
Deacon Frost.
进来吧
You can come in now.
你是吸血族的耻辱 弗劳斯特
我们若违反条约
或是聚众集会
人类政府就会找我们麻烦
你若是纯种吸血鬼就会了解
刀锋已经够麻烦了
你的舞厅太危险
These nightclubs of yours are dangerous.
是吗?
Are they?
引来太多注意力
They draw needless attention to our kind.
- 你知道规矩  - 那不是我的规矩
- You know our policy.  - Your policy, not mine.
为了生存
Our livelihood...
我们必须融入人群...
depends on our ability to blend in...
安分守己
and our discretion.
别再这么孬种了
Maybe it's time we forgot about discretion.
我们应该统治人类...
We should be ruling the humans...
不是跟他们签什么条约
not running around making back-alley treaties with them.
人类是我们的食物 不是盟友
For fuck's sake, these people are our food not our allies.
- 你太过份了  - 是吗?
- You're out of line.  - Am I?
也许我说出你们心里的话
Or maybe I'm just the first to say out loud what we've all been thinkin'.
几千年来我们都是这样生活
We have existed this way for thousands of years.
你凭什么批评我们?
Who are you to challenge our ways?
你不是纯种吸血鬼
You're not even a pureblood.
这重要吗
Like it matters.
我生来就是吸血鬼...
I was born a vampire...
每位长老都跟我一样...
as was every other member of this house...
可是你 弗劳斯特...
but, you, Frost...
你不过是半路出家
you were merely turned.
世界是我们的 不是人类的
The world belongs to us not the humans.
你很清楚
You know that.
还有什么事吗?
Do we have any other business to discuss?
我们得谈谈海外帐户
Well, there's the matter of our offshore accounts.
你有没有转帐…
And have you made the transfer to...
盖塔罗...
Gitano...
有一天你会发现你已绝种
you may wake up one day and find yourself extinct.
(蒜精)
你来早了一礼拜
You're a week early.
是啊
Yeah.
惠斯勒说 我对血清产生抵抗力
Whistler says I'm building up a resistance to the serum.
我早知道会这样
I figured that might happen.
你要保重?
You take care, all right?
我老了心也软...
I must be getting soft in my old age...
竟然让你带她回来
Ietting you bring home a stray like that.
你这么做很蠢 也许是好事
It was damn stupid of you. Might've lucked out, though.
我查过她的身份
I checked her background.
她是血液学医师
It turns out she's a hematologist.
也许能帮我们
She might be useful to us.
我看不见得
I doubt it.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
我看过她的笔记
I took a look at that notebook of hers.
她有所发现
She's onto something.
我得增加剂量
I had to increase the dose.
五十多毫克 越来越危险
It's over 50 milligrams now. That's getting dangerous.
快注射吧 老头
Just do it, old man.
迷路了吗 大夫?
Wander off the beaten path, doctor?
- 你们是什么人?  - 我叫亚伯拉汗·惠斯勒
- Who are you people?  - My name's Abraham Whistler.
你见过刀锋
You've met Blade.
- 我是囚犯吗?  - 不是
- So, am I a prisoner here?  - Not at all.
我们只是需要做好预防措施才能放你走
We just had to take certain precautions before we let you go.
你要知道 他们无所不在
You got to understand they're everywhere.
吸血鬼…
Vampires...
夜行人类
the hominus nocturna.
我们猎杀他们…
We hunt them, you see...
从一个城市到另一个城市 追踪他们的活动
moving from one city to the next tracking their migrations.
他们能重生 很难赶尽杀绝
They're hard to kill. They tend to regenerate.
难道我会相信吗?
And I'm supposed to believe all this?
你在医院见过烤肉先生
You already met Mr. Crispy at the hospital.
你说呢?
What do you think?
用什么武器?
So, what do you use, then?
- 木棍? 十字架?  - 十字架没有用
- Stakes? Crosses?  - Crosses don't do squat.
不过有些传说是真的
Some of the legends are true, though.
吸血鬼对银过敏
Vampires are severely allergic to silver.
碰到大蒜也会过敏性休克
Feed them garlic and they go into anaphylactic shock.
他们也怕阳光 紫外线
Then, of course, there's always sunlight, ultraviolet rays.
我做了这玩意 今晚试试吧?
I got this sucker running. You want to give it a try tonight?
太重了
It's still heavy.
你这么壮 还在乎吗
Well, you're so big.
你要是想再多活一天 就在天黑前赶快离开这小镇
If you want to live to see another day you'll be out of town by nightfall.
我要去哪里?
So where am I supposed to go?
他们认得你
You've been exposed to them.
或早或晚 他们一定会派人杀你
One way or another, somebody's going to take you out.
这是一场大战 我 刀锋和少数战士...
There's a war going on out there. Blade, myself, a few others...
试着阻止他们危害人类
we've tried to keep it from spilling over onto the streets.
你这种人只是倒霉被扯进来
Sometimes, people like yourself get caught in the cross fire.
我有血液样本 我去报警
I have blood samples. I can go to the police.
警察被他们收买
They own the police.
要知道 他们无孔不入
You have to understand, they're everywhere.
你一定见过他们 只是你不知道而已…
Chances are you've seen them yourself and didn't know it...
地铁站 酒吧
on the subway or in a bar.
就这样?
So that's it?
帮我包扎好就叫我滚蛋?
You guys just patch me up and send me on my way?
拿去 防吸血鬼喷液…
Here. Vampire mace...
银亚硝酸盐和蒜精
silver nitrate, essence of garlic.
眼睛睁大点 小心
You keep your eyes open. Be careful.
还有一件事…
One other thing...
买一把枪
buy yourself a gun.
当你开始怕阳光...
If you start getting sensitive to daylight...
无论喝多少水都觉得渴...
If you find you're thirsty, regardle how much you had to drink...
我就建议你举枪自尽
then I suggest you take that gun and use it on yourself.
总比变吸血鬼好
Better that than the alternative.
我警告过你
You have been warned before.
资料库只能让长老使用
These archives are restricted to the members of the house.
你在浪费时间 这种语言已失传
You are wasting your time. It's a dead language.
无法翻译这些古书
The ancient texts can never be translated.
反正你也看不懂
You wouldn't even understand them.
该死的 弗劳斯特 我在跟你说话
Damn it, Frost! I'm talking to you!
小声点 盖塔罗
Keep your voice down, Gitano.
这是图书馆 请勿高声喧哗
We're in a library. You don't need to shout.
你在打什么主意 弗劳斯特?
What are you up to, Frost?
你能把我怎样?
What are you going to do?
怎么样?
What?
你没这能耐
You bore me.
记住我们说的话
Remember what we told you.
眼睛放亮点 他们无所不在
You keep your eyes open. They're everywhere.
现在可是白天
But it's daytime!
你还好吗?
How you doing?
你好
Hi, there.
对不起 慢着
I'm sorry. Whoa! Hold on.
我是警察 对不起?
Police officer. I'm sorry, OK?
我是警察 我不是故意的 门没有关
Police officer. I didn't mean to scare you. The front door was open.
- 有什么事?  - 这是例行巡逻
- What are you doing in here?  - I'm just here on a routine check.
我是42分局的克雷格警官
Look, I'm Officer Krieger, 42nd precinct.
你是卡伦·杰森?
You're Karen Jenson, right?
医院说你昨晚遭人绑架
Your coworkers at the hospital said that you were kidnapped last night.
你没事吧?
Are you OK?
另一名医生呢?
What happened to the other doctor I was with?
韦勃·寇特斯?
Curtis Webb?
他死了
He died.
你不必替他担心?
Don't worry about that right now, OK?
为什么?
Why?
因为你也死定了
Because you're dead, too, you bitch.
可恶 这是什么?
Bitch! What is it?
这是大蒜吗?
What is this, garlic?
对 他说能对付吸血鬼
Yeah. He said it would work against vampires.
吸血鬼?
Vampires?
谁说我是吸血鬼?
Who said I was a vampire?
没有人
Nobody.
他是亲鬼族…
He's a familiar...
一心想当吸血鬼
a vampire wannabe.
要是他能证明自己... 够忠心
If he's loyal... and he proves himself,
主人也许会让他变吸血鬼
maybe his master will turn him.
等等 你拿我当诱饵?
Wait a minute. You used me as bait?
看开点
Get over it.
有这必要吗?
Is all that necessary?
这是吸血族的记号
That's a glyph... a vampire cattle brand.
克雷格警官是某人的奴才
It means that Officer Krieger is somebody's property.
要是他受到其他吸血鬼欺负...
Another vampire tries to bleed this little hooker...
主人就会出面解决
then they have to answer to his owner.
狄肯·弗劳斯特 我们一直在找他
Deacon Frost. We've been tracking him for a long time.
好了
All right.
克雷格警官 当个好猎犬?
Officer Krieger, you going to be a good little bloodhound, huh?
把你主人招出来
Tell us what your master's been up to.
你抢他 也想抢我吗?
Great, now you robbing him. You going to rob me, too?
干这行也得赚钱?
How do you think we fund this organization?
我们又不是慈善机构
We're not exactly the March of Dimes.
冒牌货
It's fake.
看样子 这小子在送血
Looks like our friend here has been blood running.
希邦诊所 我知道这地方 是个血库
Hillbarn clinic. I know this place. It's a blood bank.
吸血鬼开的 每个城市都有
Owned by vampires, and there's one in every city.
随叫随送 你要送到哪里?
And they always deliver. So, where were you taking it?
我不知道 你在鬼扯些什么…
I don't know what you're talking...
冷静点
Look, take it easy.
我再问一次
I'm only going to ask you one more time.
- 你要送到哪里?  - 他妈的去死吧
- Where were you taking it?  - Go fuck yourself.
你他妈的才去死
Fuck me? No, you fuck this.
你最好弄清楚状况
You better wake up.
这一切都是表面的
The world you live in is just a sugar-coated topping.
另外有一个残酷的世界
There is another world beneath it... the real world.
你想活下去就得学着狠下心扣扳机
And if you want to survive it you better learn to pull the trigger.
- 等一下 我跟你去  - 你对我没用
- Wait a minute. I'm comin' with you.  - You're useless.
我得跟着你
I have to stick with you.
这样我才能活下去找到解药
It's the only way I'll stay alive long enough to find a cure for myself.
没有解药的
There is no cure.
他不会回来
He's not going to come back.
他没有那么蠢
Nobody's that stupid.
当你了解他的本性...
When you understand the nature of a thing...
就知道他有多蠢
you know what it's capable of.
克雷格 代号16009
It's Krieger. I'm at 16-0-0-9.
快接珍珠
Get me Pearl.
珍珠在进食
Pearl's feeding.
我替弗劳斯特送货时碰到刀锋
I got a delivery in progress here and I just had a run-in with Blade.
你们马上撤离诊所
I got to clear out that clinic on Hillhurst now!
事情有眉目了 那就是吸血鬼的记号
Looks like we hit pay dirt. That's a vampire mark.
附近有他们的藏身处…
It means there's a safe house around here somewhere...
天亮了就躲起来
a place they can go with donors coming.
那些泊车小弟? 全是吸血鬼 门房也是...
See the valets over there? They're vampires. So is the doorman...
街角的妓女也是
and the whore on the corner.
- 你怎么知道?  - 看他们的动作...
- How can you tell?  - By the way they move...
闻他们的味道
the way they smell.
这像是场噩梦
It's like a bad dream.
今晚 有些人比吸血鬼更危险
There are worse things out tonight than vampires.
- 什么人?  - 我
- Like what?  - Like me.
吸血鬼知识入门
OK, vampire anatomy 101.
十字架和圣水一点也没有用...
Crosses and holy water don't do dick...
所以 忘了你在电影里看到的吧
so forget what you've seen in the movies.
他们怕木棍 银钉和阳光
You use a stake, silver, or sunlight.
你会用枪吗?
You know how to use one of these?
不会 但我学得很快
Nope, but I'll damn sure learn quick.
按掉保险锁 子弹已经上膛…
The safety's off, rounds already chambered...
银弹装满蒜精
silver hollow point filled with garlic.
射中头或心脏 否则你就完蛋
You aim for the head or the heart. Anything else is your ass.
你有邀请函吗?
Do you have an invitation?
- 入口在哪里?  - 我不能说
- Where's the entrance?  - I can't tell you that, man.
我再问一次 入口呢?
I'm going to ask you one more time. Where's the entrance?
好啦 好啦
OK. OK.
在冰箱
It's in the freezer.
我说过了 入口在冰箱
Come on, man! I told you! It's in the fridge!
传话给弗劳斯特
You give Frost a message from me.
我要对吸血鬼大开杀戒
You tell him it's open season on all suckheads.
好大的资料库
Some kind of archive.
记录一定藏在这里
This must be where they keep most of their records.
这么高科技?
Isn't this just a little high-tech?
他们渗透进了各行各业…
They've got their claws into everything...
政治 财经 房地产
politics, finance, real estate.
市中心一半是他们的
They already own half of downtown.
- 弗劳斯特的聚会真酷  - 是啊  但他人呢?
- Frost throws a good party.  - Yeah, but where is he?
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
(完成翻译)
别让客人久等
Don't keep everyone waiting.
狄肯 有人找你
Deacon, there's someone here to see you.
我得跟你谈谈 弗劳斯特
I got to talk to you, Frost.
对不起 我非来不可
I'm sorry. I had to come here.
我不该去找珍珠 我真蠢
It's a mistake going to Pearl's. I know that. Dumb fucking me.
- 你一定很生气  - 有这么明显吗?
- I know you're disappointed.  - Am I that transparent?
想见他吗? 好啊
You want to meet him? Yeah.
我跟他是好兄弟 我能帮你们介绍
I can get you guys in with him. 'Cause we're tight. We're like brothers.
妈的
Fuck.
弗劳斯特
Aw, fuck. Frost.
我刚和这些小妞说起你
I've been telling these bitches all about you.
她们很想见你
They've been dying to meet you.
这些辣妹骚得带劲…
They are so psyched. Bad ass bitches. They...
- 弗劳斯特 是刀锋  - 他在忙
- Frost, it's about Blade.  - Aw, he's busy, you know?
他一专心起来 就不会乱搞...
Because when he's focused on business...
弗劳斯特 听好
Frost, this is important.
刀锋在等我 他拿那女孩当诱饵
Blade was waiting for me using the girl as bait.
你笨得要上当
And you were stupid enough to take it.
闭嘴 婊子 我不知道他在
Shut up, bitch. I didn't know he was going to be there.
那是个圈套? 别担心
It was a trap, see? But don't worry about it.
这不是问题 我们还是能逮到那女孩
It's no problem. We can still get the girl.
别管那女孩 我要的是刀锋
Forget the girl. I want Blade.
- 我知道  - 听到吗 昆恩?
- I know you do.  - You hear me, Quinn?
我要活捉他
I want him alive.
什么?
What?
等等 你要活捉他?
Wait a minute, man. You want him alive?
什么臭味道?
What's that smell?
...你要仔细看 弗劳斯特
...image carefully, Frost.
要十二个纯种吸血鬼才行
You will need 12 purebloods to make the ritual work.
克雷格 是你吗? 他来了
Krieger, is that you? He's here!
他一定是图书馆长珍珠
This must be Pearl, the record keeper.
他会杀我 你需要我的 弗劳斯特
He's going to kill me! You need me, Frost!
珍珠 你死定了
Pearl, you're history.
但是 至少死得有点骨气吧
Have the good grace to die with some fuckin' dignity.
没用的吸血鬼
Ruthless bloodsucker.
恭喜你 刀锋
Congratulations, Blade.
弗劳斯特
Frost.
听说你在找我
I hear you've been lookin' for me.
- 我真高兴  - 你会难过的
- I'm flattered.  - It'll pass.
妈的
Fuck.
- 那是什么?  - 肥猪 这是紫外线灯
- What is that?  - That, biscuit boy, is a U.V. Lamp.
咱们要玩问答游戏
We're gonna play a little game of 20 questions.
答得好的话...
Depending on how you answer...
你只会晒黑
you may walk out of here with a tan.
那是什么?
What's that?
没什么 只是例行研究
That? Oh, it's nothing. It's routine research.
事实上那只是电子游戏
Actually, it's a video game.
一定很痛吧
That must've hurt.
这是预言的片段
It's a fragment, a piece ofthe prophecy!
什么预言?
What prophecy?
我不确定
Oh, I'm not really sure.
有太多了…
There are so many out...
血神即将降临
十二天王会唤醒血神
你没办法阻止 日行者
And there is nothing you can do about it, daywalker!
是吗?
Is that so?
那是弗劳斯特说的
Well, that's what Frost says.
不介意我借去吧?
Then you won't mind me borrowing this, will you?
他敢乱动就把他烤焦
If he moves, fry him.
- 里面是什么?  - 没什么 只是储藏室
- What's in here?  - Nothing. It's a storeroom.
别浪费时间 没什么重要的
But you're wastin' your time. There's nothing of importance to anyone.
看一下无妨
Then you won't mind if I take a peek.
他乱动
He moved.
这些是什么?
What is this?
这些是死亡之书的残页...
These are the pages from The Book of Erebus...
吸血鬼的圣经
the vampire bible.
一切都在上面...
It contains everything...
吸血鬼的历史
their entire history.
血神是他们的传说
La Magra must be one oftheir legends.
弗劳斯特为什么对血神有兴趣?
Why is Frost so interested in La Magra?
- 把手给我  - 慢着 朋友
- Give me your hand.  - Hold on, amigo!
记得我吗?
Do you remember me?
上吧
Give it to him!
干得好
Nice one.
看啊 看啊
Well, well, well.
你砍断我的手 老兄 记得吗? 不过没关系
You took my arm, man. Remember? But it's cool.
我有新的手
I got a new one.
你看我能弹钢琴吗?
Think I'll ever play piano again?
你可以砍我 你可以切我...
You can slice him, you can dice him...
但昆恩怎么样都不会死
but the Quinn man just keeps on comin'!
你们瞧
Check it out.
我拿到他的剑
I've got his pigsticker.
你这个蠢蛋
You're a fuckup, Crease!
你这个白痴
You're a fuckup!
拿到他的剑才怪
"I got his pigsticker!"
你的花样真多 对吧?
You're just full of surprises, ain't you, chief?
别惹火我...
Stay with me, sweetness...
我要把你碎尸万段
'cause I'm not finished with you yet.
这是什么
Ah, looky here.
银弹钉
Silver.
漂亮的手艺 一定花不少钱
Nice craftsmanship, huh? Probably cost you a pretty penny.
你们看 这家伙...
This here is a man who takes his job...
未免太小题大作了
just a little too seriously, don't you think?
我想起来了 刀锋 你欠我一次
Come to think of it, Blade, I owe you one.
严格说起来...
Actually, if you want to get technical...
你欠我两次
I owe you two.
有什么好笑的?
What's so funny, bright eyes?
我的伙伴来了
I'm expecting company.
- 逮个你们正着?  - 不 别开枪
- Catch you fuckers at a bad time?  - No! No guns!
笨蛋 这里
No! Fuckin' this way!
放下枪
Drop the guns!
我需要他
I need him!
抓活的 快去
He wants Blade alive! Go!
- 你一直都在听?  - 我们保持聊络
- Ya've been listenin' in the whole time?  - Keepin' radio contact.
我才不会让他独闯的?
Think I'd let him run loose without a chaperone?
我太老了
Christ! I'm too old for this.
我得坐轮椅
Somebody get me a goddamn wheelchair.
他能照顾自己
He can take care of himself.
快跳
Jump!
你打算怎样?
What are you gonna do?
我的天
Oh, my God.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
脱臼了
It's dislocated.
让我来
Let me help you.
- 我来...  - 不用 走开
- Let me give you...  - No! Get away.
你也是吸血鬼?
You're one of them, aren't you?
不是 我不同
No. I'm something else.
当年他才十三岁 流落街头...
I found him when he was 13. He'd been livin' on the streets...
吸流浪汉的血
feedin' off the homeless.
他不吸血就活不下去
His need for blood had taken hold at puberty.
我以为他是吸血鬼
I took him for a vampire at first.
差点杀了他 后来才搞清楚
Almost killed him, too. Then I realized what he was.
他母亲怀孕时被吸血鬼咬到
Blade's mother was attacked by a vampire while she was pregnant.
她死了 而他却活了下来
She died, but he lived.
可是他的基因发生突变
Unfortunately, he'd undergone certain genetic changes.
他不怕大蒜 银...
He can withstand garlic, silver...
连阳光都不怕...
even sunlight...
他有吸血鬼的力量
and he's got their strength.
他的伤口明天就能愈合
This time tomorrow, all his wounds will be healed.
他像人类一样会衰老
He still ages like a human, though.
吸血鬼却衰老得很慢
Vampires age slower than us.
不幸的是 他遗传吸血鬼的嗜血性
Unfortunately, he also inherited their thirst.
我以为血清能抑制
I thought the serum was supposed to suppress that.
时间一久
Time's runnin' out.
他的身体产生抵抗力
His body's startin' to reject it.
我一直找不到解药
So far, all my efforts to find a cure have failed.
你为何猎杀他们?
Why do you hunt them?
我曾有过家庭…
I had a family once...
妻子和两个女儿
a wife and 2 daughters.
有一天来了个流浪汉...
Then a drifter came callin' one evenin'...
他是吸血鬼
a vampire.
他先玩弄她们...
He toyed with 'em first...
逼我决定让哪一个先死
tried to make me decide which order they'd die in.
我们下手绝不留情 不过越打越辛苦
We kill as many of 'em as we can find, but it's gettin' worse.
因为弗劳斯特
Because of Frost.
吸血鬼族内部发生权力争斗
There's somethin' happenin' in the vampire ranks.
会有一场大乱...
It's somethin' big...
我打赌那臭小子一定是祸源
and I'd stake my life that son of a bitch is at the center of it.
刀锋
Blade.
惠斯勒都告诉我了
Whistler told me what happened.
我知道你的身份
He told me what you are.
你不知道 你根本就不了解我
You don't know me. You don't know anything about me.
我不是人类
I'm not human.
- 你像是个人类  - 人类不会吸血
- You look human to me...  - Humans don't drink blood.
那是以前的事
That was a long time ago.
你应该忘了它
Maybe you should let that go.
我一直在寻找害死我母亲的那个吸血鬼
I've spent my whole life lookin' for that thing that killed my mother.
让我变成现在这样
It made me what I am.
每次除掉一个吸血鬼...
And every time I take one of those monsters out...
我就更接近人类...
I get a little piece of that life back...
别叫我忘了它
so don't you tell me about forgetting.
他让我们措手不及
He took us by surprise!
他们两个人解决了你所有的保安?
Two of them against your entire security force?
别都怪在我头上 你当时也在
Don't put that shit on me, 'cause you were there, too!
我想狄肯会感激的…
I'm sure Deacon will appreciate...
...我可是还挨了一刀
...stabbed in the balls for it, all right?
你这小贱货
You little skeez!
你断手是活该
Don't see the lifestyle really suits you.
小心我把你揍扁
I should put this stump through that shit-eating grin of yours.
面对现实吧 你太差劲了 算你活该
Face it. You were sloppy. You got what you deserved.
狄肯 让我宰了那家伙 你看他对我做了什么
Deacon, let me take this guy out. Look what he fuckin' did!
- 他又砍断我的手  - 听我说 我要活捉他
- He took my hand again!  - Listen to me. I want him alive.
你他妈的在说什么呀 活捉?
What the fuck are you talk... You want him alive?
我们一直想除掉他
We've been tryin' to kill this motherfucker for years.
你他妈的疯了不成?
Are you out of your fuckin' mind?
傻瓜 别紧张
Big guy, relax.
耐心等
Be patient.
我们有得忙了
Now, we got a lot to do here.
我需要你
I need you, man.
I need you.
早安
Morning.
还好吗?
How you feelin'?
你看看
Look at that.
天气挺热的
Whew. Gettin' a little toasty out here, huh?
你有多久 没看过日出了?
When was the last time you stopped to appreciate a good sunrise?
对了 你天生是吸血鬼...
Oh, that's right. You were born a vampire...
所以你从没看过日出 对吗?
so you never had the pleasure, have you?
没关系
That's OK. It's all right.
我们一起分享这一刻...
Least we're here together. Share the moment...
我觉得很感动
which means a lot to me by the way, really.
是真的 若你能多了解我...
I mean that. 'Cause actually, when you get to know me...
就会知道我的感情丰富
I'm a fairly sentimental type of guy.
而且有点天真
Bit of an innocent, you might say.
你要什么 弗劳斯特
Do what you want, Frost.
这不重要了
Doesn't make any difference.
你就是他妈的不明白
You just don't fuckin' get it.
- 你不能成为纯种吸血鬼  - 抓住他
- You're never gonna be a pureblood.  - Hold him.
你统治不了我们
You will never rule us!
老天
Jesus Christ.
- 祝你愉快  - 抱歉
- Have a nice day.  - Sorry, you old dog.
你太伶牙俐齿了
You just got a little too long in the tooth.
干嘛 很好笑呀
What, man? That was funny.
伶牙利齿 真好笑
"Long, tooth." Funny.
我和你说过...
Did I tell you the one about...
你把盖塔罗怎么了?
What have you done with Dragonetti?
我们谈正事吧
Let's get down to business, shall we?
我要十二名志愿者
I need 12 volunteers.
这是什么?
What is this?
好像有人用来擦屁股
Smells like a vampire wiped his ass with it.
- 资料库拿来的  - 用血写的字
- I took it from the archives.  - It's written in blood.
这是死亡之书
It's from The Book of Erebus.
弗劳斯特一直在翻译
I think it's what Frost has been workin' on.
跟血神和十二天王有关
It's somethin' about the Blood God the Spirits ofthe Twelve.
其他的看不出来
I don't know. I can't make out the rest of it.
也许这有帮助
Maybe this'll help.
我会查出来
I'll figure out something.
这些是什么?
So what's all this?
昨晚我回医院一趟...
Took a trip to the hospital last night...
借来一些仪器
borrowed some equipment.
你的神奇解药?
For your miracle cure?
这是抗血凝剂
This is E.D.T.A. It's an anticoagulant.
用来治疗血块
We use it to treat blood clots.
看看会发生什么 我把它滴入...
Now look what happens when I introduce it...
吸血鬼的血液
onto a sample of vampire blood.
退后一步
Take a step back.
会引起强烈反应
The reaction's energetic.
- 好厉害的解药  - 抗血凝剂不是解药
- Some cure.  - I didn't say E.D.T.A. was a cure.
你能用来轰掉吸血鬼的脑袋
But maybe you could use it to explode some vampire heads.
等等 我要抽点你的血
Wait a minute. I need a sample ofyour blood.
待会吧 我得到市中心
Later. Gotta go downtown.
- 我需要血清  - 先别急
- Need some serum.  - Serum can wait.
这很重要
This is important.
- 他病了?  - 癌症
- Is he sick?  - Cancer.
你们感情很好 对吧?
You have a lot of love for him, don't you?
我们合作无间
We have a good arrangement.
他制造武器 我则大展身手
He makes the weapons. I use 'em.
我母亲常说...
My mother used to say...
哀莫大于心死
"a cold heart is a dead heart."
你的脸色很差
You don't look so good.
我只是有点累
I'm just a little tired.
我们忙了一整晚
You know we've been workin' all night.
没有及时阻止你的变化
I guess we didn't catch it in time.
你只剩一天...
You got another day...
最多两天
two at the most.
我感到很遗憾
For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
听起来 你好像把我当成了死人
You make it sound like I'm already dead.
你好吗 老兄
How you doin', chief?
别乱来
Easy.
别让小朋友...
Wouldn't want our little friend here...
成为失踪儿童
to wind up on the back of a milk carton, would we?
很高兴终于见到你 我一直在注意你
It's nice to finally meet you. Had my eye on you for years.
我把你摸透了 血清 惠斯勒 我都一清二楚
I know all about you... your serum, Whistler... everything.
- 防晒油  - 这只是暂时的
- Sunblock.  - Hey, it's a start, right?
我想要成为你这种人... 日行者
The goal, of course, is to be like you... the daywalker.
两种人的好处都有
You got the best of both worlds, don't you?
你有我们的优点 没有缺点
All our strengths none of our weaknesses.
我可不这么想
Maybe I don't see it that way.
别假装你是人类?
Oh, so it's back to pretending we're human again?
少来这套 别当叛徒
Come on. Spare me the Uncle Tom routine, OK?
别忘了自己的本性
You can't keep denying what you are, man.
人类会接受你这个杂种吗?
You think the humans will ever accept a half-breed like you?
不会的 他们害怕你
They can't. They're afraid ofyou.
这是应该的
And they should be.
你是只该死的发狂野兽
You're an animal. You're a fuckin' maniac.
看看他们 全都是肉牛...
Look at 'em. They're cattle...
我们的食物
pieces of meat.
管他们这么多干嘛
What difference does it make how their world ends?
瘟疫 战争 饥荒
Plague, war, famine.
别谈什么仁义道德
Morality doesn't even enter into it.
我们是物竞天择的结果
We're just a function of natural selection, man...
全新人种
the new race.
你的妆糊掉了
Looks like your mascara's running.
我要跟你握手言和 我要你加入我们
I'm offering you a truce. I want you with us.
你当我是白痴吗?
What do you think, I'm stupid?
十二天王
将唤醒血神
你知道血神的事
You're familiar with the Blood God.
弗劳斯特
Frost.
对我来说...
You're nothing to me...
你只是一个死吸血鬼
but another dead vampire.
你很傻 知道吗?
You're an idiot. You know that?
我想饶你一条小命...
I came down here offering you an easy way out...
你他妈的却不知好歹
and you spit it right back in my fuckin' face.
别乱来
Careful.
我才不管她死活? 他们只是食物...
What do I care? They're nothing but cattle...
就像你说的
just like you said.
你想来硬的尽管来...
If you wanna take the hard road, be my guest...
不过我向你保证 当这一切结束的时候...
but I promise you, by the time this is over...
你会求生不得求死不能…
you're gonna wish they never cut you from your mother's...
快回家
Go home.
很简单 吸血鬼为何吸血?
It was simple. Why do vampires need to drink blood?
他们无法吸收血红素
'Cause their own blood can't sustain hemoglobin.
这跟溶血性贫血一样是遗传病
Right. It's a genetic defect, just like hemolytic anemia.
也就是说 我们一定要用基因治疗法...
That means that we have to treat it with gene therapy...
用还原病毒更改遗传基因
rewrite the victim's DNA with a retrovirus.
镰状细胞性贫血也是这么治疗
They've been using it on sickle cell anemia.
- 这安全吗?  - 不知道...
- Are you sure that's safe?  - I have no idea...
可是我别无选择?
but I don't have a choice, do l?
- 你真的认为有效?  - 对我来说... 有效
- You actually think this could work?  - On me... yes.
对刀锋来说就不一定
On Blade, I'm not so sure.
他不像我是被吸血鬼咬到
He didn't contract vampirism from a bite like I did.
他是天生的 这是他的遗传基因
He was born with it. It's part of his DNA.
我能治好嗜血症 得花点时间
I'm sure I can cure his thirst, but it's gonna take time.
没有时间了
Ah, we're out oftime.
你看到磁盘的内容
You saw what was on that disk.
该死的
Damn.
快离开这里
Get out of here.
我叫你快离开这里
I said get out of here!
很棒的地方 挺难找的
Nice place. Took us a while to find it!
- 快咬我吧  - 我不会咬你
- Bite me and get it over with.  - I ain't gonna bite you.
交给你了
Do your thing.
惠斯勒
Whistler.
她被弗劳斯特抓走
Frost took her.
听我说
Listen to me.
磁盘
The disk.
被我们破解了
He decoded it.
弗劳斯特想要...
Frost is trying to...
造成世界末日
trigger a fuckin' vampire apocalypse.
他一直想要...
There's some kind of...
让吸血鬼的神复活
vampire God he's trying to resurrect.
血神
La Magra.
你就是关键
You're the key.
他需要你的血...
He needs your blood...
一个日行者的血
the blood of the daywalker.
你是血神的选民
You're the chosen one.
听我说 刀锋
Listen to me, Blade.
- 别去找他  - 办不到
- You can't go after him.  - Bullshit.
你若落在弗劳斯特手上...
If Frost gets his hands on you...
人类就会灭亡
it's all over.
吸血族将占领地球
There'll be armies ofthe motherfuckers.
可恶
Shit.
你一定要把我杀死
You're gonna have to finish me off.
别让我变吸血鬼
Don't want me coming back.
先治好你的伤
We can treat the wounds.
我没有救了
It's too far gone.
你很清楚
You know that.
把枪给我
Give me your gun.
不
No.
把你的枪给我
Give me the goddamn gun.
给我滚吧 臭小子
Now walk away, you stupid son of a bitch.
快走吧
Walk the fuck away.
当你看到这个的时候 惠斯勒应该早就死了
By the time you watch this, your friend Whistler should be dead.
你要知道 他死命抵抗
If it makes any difference to you, he put up quite a fight.
你能在埃奇伍德塔找到我们
You can find us at the Edgewood Towers.
你好像有点拘束 你太紧张...
You seem a bit tense. A bit pent-up maybe...
得发泄一下
Iike you need to release something.
不是吗? 刀锋没有让你爽到吗?
You know? Blade not givin' it to you maybe?
我想不透...
I don't know. I just...
你是个大美女
I see such a beautiful woman.
皮肤这么嫩
Great skin.
我只想让你快乐
I'd like to see you happy, that's all.
你要把我变成吸血鬼?
Is this the part where you offer to turn me?
要不然就得杀你
It's either that or a body bag.
来呀 尽管咬我吧
Go ahead. Bite me.
我有解药
I'll just cure myself.
上次能治好 这次也行
I did it before, and I can do it again.
- 没有解药的 宝贝  - 被咬到就有...
- There is no cure, baby.  - There is if you've been bitten...
只要你曾是个人类
if you were once human.
你怎么会有伤疤 狄肯?
How'd you get that scar, Deacon?
天生的吸血鬼不会有伤疤
A born vampire would have the power to regenerate from birth.
你一定是后来才变的
You must've gotten scarred before you were turned.
对不对?
Isn't that right?
你不是真的吸血鬼
Vampires like you aren't a species.
你只是受到感染 像是性病或是病毒
You're just infected a virus, a sexually transmitted disease.
你知道我们是什么
I'll tell you what we are, sister.
我们是世界的主宰 血神要降临...
We're the top ofthe fuckin' food chain. The Blood God's coming...
今晚过后 人类将灭亡
and after tonight, you people are fuckin' history.
血神就像一阵龙卷风
He's a hurricane, an act of God.
碰到它就会变成吸血鬼
Anyone caught in his path will instantly be turned.
你的朋友 亲人 都不能幸免
Everyone you've ever known... everyone you've ever fucking loved.
不管是纯种或是杂种
It won't matter who's pureblood and who's not.
你能救全世界吗?
How are you gonna cure the whole fuckin' world?
刀锋的血是关键
And Blade's blood is the key.
有人闯进来
We got an intruder.
你不了解 他很厉害
I don't think you understand. This dude is fuckin' bad.
二十个人都挡不了 他会丢刀子什么的
He had 20 guys around him... and he's got shit he throws at you...
是啊 丢旋风刀
Yeah, the swords.
而且耍得哧哧叫
Throw it in the air, catch it underneath.
你他妈的给我闭嘴
Yeah. Shut the fuck up!
目前没发现入侵者
There's no intruder where we are.
搞定他 明白吗? 他只有一个人
Look, make it happen, all right? It's one guy on foot.
他来了 抓住他
That's him! Get him!
怎么会有枪声?
Why am I hearing gunfire?
我说过 我要活捉他
Did I tell anybody to start shooting? I need him alive.
求求你
Please!
我不是吸血鬼
I just work for them!
- 老天 全面封锁  - 是的
- Jesus Christ. Lock this place down.  - Yes, sir!
艾力克?
Eric?
你不是死了
But you died.
那天晚上 我就活过来...
I came back, Eric. That very same night...
狄肯完全接纳我
when Deacon welcomed me into his arms.
我以为你会很高兴
Jesus Christ. I thought you'd be happy.
你好不容易和母亲团聚
You're finally reunited, and you act like this?
刀锋 投降吧 你玩完了
Blade, give it up. It's over.
她是我的 老兄
She belongs to me, buddy.
别这么吃惊
Don't look so surprised.
你一生在找...
You spent your whole life...
咬你老妈的吸血鬼
Iooking for the vampire who bit your mother.
就是我
Well, here I am.
没想到你会活下来
Who would ever guess you'd survive your mother's death?
现在我们又聚在一起…
But you did. And here we are...
幸福快乐的一家人
one big happy fuckin' family.
我需要血清
I need my serum.
我逃出去就注射你的解药
Maybe when we get outta this, I'll take that miracle cure of yours.
但是会有副作用
There's one catch.
若是有效...
If it works...
你将失去超人力量和重生能力
you'll lose your strength and your ability to regenerate.
完全变成人类
You'll be completely human.
刀锋 卡伦
Blade, Karen
- 欢迎你们大驾光临  - 谢谢你的墨镜
- Glad you could make it.  - Thanks for the shades.
我们的祖先称它为永夜殿
Our ancestors called this place the temple of eternal night.
很棒吧?
Nice, isn't it?
这些天才忘了有这地方
Apparently, these geniuses forgot it ever existed.
幸好...
Fortunately for us...
我很爱钻研历史
I'm what you might call a student of history.
为什么来这?
Why are we here?
永夜殿是为了这一刻而建…
This temple was built for one glorious moment...
今天晚上 迎接血神降临
this night, for the Blood God.
谢了
Thanks.
我看看你的剑
Let's see this sword ofyours.
钛合金打造? 精心雕刻?
Titanium, right? Acid-etched?
真的很好用
I'll get used to a weapon like this.
怎么?
What?
你好像很吃惊
You look surprised.
我说过 刀锋 我对你一清二楚
I told you, Blade, I know everything about you.
- 伸出手 昆恩  - 为什么? 我的手好得很
- Hold out your arm, Quinn.  - Why, man? They're, like, all better.
伸出手 快点
Hold out your arm. Now.
狄肯 我...
Deacon, l...
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
他在耍我 他妈的只是在耍我
He was fuckin' with me.
刀锋
Blade.
他只想要吸血 听不见你的
He can't hear you, honey. The thirst has got him now.
这是什么? 你的血清
What do we have here? The precious serum.
你有多久没有注射了? 十二或十三个钟头?
How long's it been since you shot up? 12, 13 hours maybe?
你一定很想吸血?
I bet you're just dying for a drink, aren't you?
感觉如何?
What's it feel like?
- 全身的血在沸腾?  - 你试试看
- Is your blood on fire?  - Try some.
你也许会喜欢
You might like it.
谢了 我爱吸鲜血
Thanks, but I prefer the real thing.
反正...
In any event...
你不再需要它了
I don't think you'll be needing these anymore.
真可惜
It's a shame, you know?
你本来是吸血鬼...
When I think ofwhat you've become...
现在却变成这样 这不能怪你
what you should have become. I guess I don't blame you.
所有的一切...
I mean, with everything that's happened...
都是人类的弱点在作祟
it's the human side ofyou that's made you weak.
你应该回归本性
You should've listened to your blood.
随便你怎么说...
Say what you want...
日出前你一定会死
but, I promise you, you'll be dead by dawn.
把他带出去
Get him outta here.
把那些浑蛋带下去
Get these fucks downstairs. Now.
快点 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
我们走
Let's go.
别担心 甜心 我没忘记你
Don't worry, sweetheart. We haven't forgotten about you.
宝贝
Oh, no, baby.
我对你有很特别的安排
We got something real special planned for you.
那冲浪小子的屁股真翘 我把他吸干了
That surfer boy had a nice ass. I sucked him dry.
- 这家伙被我吸后应该会变  - 可是他并没变吸血鬼
- And you'd figure he'd turn, man.  - Yeah, but he didn't turn, did he?
没有 但他却变成僵尸 有时是会这样的
No. He turned into some kinda zombie. It happens sometimes, cutie.
他被吓呆了
He was fuckin' tripped out.
真可怜
Pathetic.
这种人渣什么都吃
These guys are complete scum. They'll eat anything...
动物 老鼠 尸体 有时候...
animals, rodents, corpses, and sometimes...
- 连吸血鬼都吃  - 那最好了
- they'll even eat vampires.  - That's a plus.
说了这么多...
And bearing that all in mind...
现在要你见见老朋友了
I'd like you to meet an old friend of yours.
真可惜 我挺喜欢她
It's too bad. I kinda liked her.
真是浪费
What a waste.
我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what's happening to me.
没有脉博
No pulse.
而且肤色很苍白
And, of course there's the question of lividity.
寇特斯?
Curtis?
卡伦?
Karen?
卡伦
Karen.
没想到会再见到你
I never thought I would see you again.
告诉我 卡伦 你有没有后悔跟我分手?
Tell me, Karen do you ever have second thoughts about us?
可怜的孩子
Poor child.
你病得很重
You're so sick.
饥渴欲狂
So thirsty.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
艾力克 看着我
Eric, look at me.
现在我是吸血族的一份子
Vampires are my people now. I'm one of them.
你不是
Can't be.
我当然是
Yes, it can.
你要知道
Try to understand, Eric.
你母亲早就死了
Your mother died a long time ago.
我杀过人...
I've hunted...
吸过血...
I've killed...
我很喜欢
and I've enjoyed it.
你不喜欢吗?
Haven't you?
你一定喜欢
I know you have.
你一定会变成吸血鬼的
Sooner or later, the thirst always wins.
来吧
Come on.
叫他们站好
Spread them out.
每个记号上站一个人
One on each glyph, under the towers.
一定要站好
Make it perfect.
把电梯叫上来
Bring the elevator up.
傻姑娘
You stupid girl.
你真以为 血神会降临吗?
What do you think is going to happen? La Magra? The Blood God?
那只是吸血鬼的童话
That's a fairy tale for pretty little vampires.
你干嘛这么害怕?
Then why are you sweating, pureblood?
怕我偷走你的灵魂...
You're afraid we're gonna steal your soul...
纯种吸血鬼的精华?
your pureblood spirit?
你应该害怕 去读预言吧
You should be. Read the prophecy.
你们该有所贡献了
It's time you fucks contributed something to the cause.
就算弗劳斯特说得没错 他才不理你
Even if Frost is right, you really think he cares about you?
你死定了 就像我们一样
You're gonna die just like the rest of us.
刀锋
Blade.
今晚人类将灭亡
Tonight, the age of man comes to an end.
不能妥协
No more compromises.
我们会成为神
We're gonna be gods.
当然了
Of course we are.
我要当恶神 我要当邪恶的吸血神
I'm gonna be naughty. I'm gonna be a naughty vampire god.
一定要阻止...
Gotta stop...
阻止...
stop...
省点力气
Save your strength.
你的体温过低 会流血致死
You're hypovolemic. You're bleeding to death.
我需要... 血清
Need... serum.
刀锋
Blade.
听我说
Listen to me.
我要你吸我的血
I want you to take some of my blood.
不行
No.
不
快吸吧
Look, just do it.
把你的臭手拿开
大家渴了吗? 希望你们都很渴
Is everybody thirsty? I hope you're all very fucking thirsty.
不要停
Don't stop.
继续吸
不要停
Don't stop.
继续吸
滋味如何?
How was it?
艾力克
Eric.
我是你母亲
I'm your mother.
你不会杀我...
You wouldn't hurt your mother...
对吧?
would you?
过来
Come here.
我要解除你的痛苦
I must release you.
狄肯
Deacon.
我不再是狄肯了
Not anymore.
弗劳斯特
Frost!
- 杀了他  - 慢着 你欠我的 老兄
- Kill him.  - Wait! I owe you, man.
我有两只手 刀锋
I got two new hands, Blade.
我不知道该用哪只杀你
I don't know which one to use to kill you with!
杀了你一定很爽快
I'm really going to enjoy this now.
刀锋
Blade.
决斗吧
Let's do this.
你太迟了 刀锋
You're too late, Blade.
轮到我了
My turn.
看看你 你这个婊子
Look at you. You're a little bitch.
你的血清? 帮不了你了
What, your serum? It can't help you now, stud.
好准头
Nice shot.
有些笨蛋硬是学不了乖
Some motherfuckers are always trying to ice-skate uphill.
刀锋
Blade.
快走吧
Let's get out of here.
要把你治好就得回实验室
I need to get back to the lab if I'm going to cure you.
事情还没有结束
It's not over.
解药留着吧
You keep your cure.
还有一场硬仗 我得再度出击
There's still a war going on and I have a job to do.
你想帮忙 那就做更好的血清
You want to help make me a better serum.
(莫斯科)
好冷哦
我们去哪里
这是个惊喜
惊喜
我最爱惊喜
你一定会喜欢这个的
我逮个你正着
同志